<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<pages>
  <page name="~/login.aspx" instance="0"><![CDATA[<h1>Authorised access only</h1>]]></page>
  <page name="~/thanks.aspx" instance="0"><![CDATA[<h1>Email sent successfully</h1>
<p>We will endeavour  to reply as soon as possible.</p>
<p><strong>Thanks</strong></p>]]></page>
  <page name="~/contact.aspx" instance="0"><![CDATA[<h1>Contact Us</h1>]]></page>
  <page name="~/default.aspx" instance="0"><![CDATA[<h1>Web Foundations</h1>
<div style="margin-top: 15px;" class="introText">If ever I need to
build a website in a day I checkout these Web Foundations as a
starting block.</div>
<p>These foundations allow me to very quickly build simple sites
that provide my clients with the ability to click an edit button
and get write access to the text on their websites. I find it
cleaner and simpler than more comprehensive solutions like
Macromedia Contribute or DotNetNuke. Its also great for inexpensive
hosting as there are no Database requirements.</p>
<p>Its basically an XML Content Management System. It uses the
Spring URL Rewriting library for search-engine URL's. FCKEditor
provides the WYSIWYG and a C# port of HTML tidy is employed to
sanitise users text.</p>
<p>I've also built a Lightbox Image Gallery that consumes Picasa
generated XML. This is included as a control so it's really easy to
drop on any page.</p>
<p>It's all build on ASP.Net Master Pages so its familiar and easy
to extend.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Courtenay Probert</strong><br />
<em>Web Foundations Lead Developer</em><br />
&nbsp;</p>]]></page>
  <page name="~/gallery.aspx" instance="0"><![CDATA[<h1>Gallery</h1>
<p>Simply drop a gallery control on the page and set the reference
to the approperate folder in the "~/Picasa"&nbsp; folder to set up
a gallery.</p>
<p><strong>Here are 2 examples:</strong></p>]]></page>
  <page name="~/p/virtual.aspx" instance="0"><![CDATA[<h1>Virtual Page</h1>
<p>This isn't a page on the file system!&nbsp; Its a virtual page
created using the URL Rewright library!</p>
<p>Great for quickly creating a new page. SSimply drop a new node
in the web.site map and voila; a new page.</p>]]></page>
</pages>